(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-25T14:02:09.547921",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Greetings, CC, my fated rival!
Greetings, Ina, my distant rival!
And hello to everyone watching from
Serendipity!
Remember, if you want a chance for your wish
to be featured on the Otomo
or the Takotachi that we made,
post about it with #WishUponTakoTomo!
Yeah!
Hey, thank you AmiAmi for supporting our rivalry,
and for supporting Serendipity!
Be sure to check out the booth at
AmiAmi Expo!
Yeah!
Hey, pawos!
And all of HoloBase is here with me, all 14 of us!
HoloBase is coming to Round1 USA locations nationwide, starting this September.
Come hang out with us!
Follow @round1usa on Instagram and X so you don't miss out on any updates!
We can't wait to see you there! Bye-bye!
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
the stars aligned like it was always meant to be
so come along and join me, embracing serendipity
one shooting star, one blaze of light
(one time in a lifetime)
one million wishes in the night
somehow, my dearest dream came true
(one time in a lifetime)
i saw this brilliant sky with you
so many roads, so many journeys
What's up everyone?
Welcome to hololive English Serendipity!
Let's take to the shore amidst melody
(one time in a lifetime)
Ready? Showtime, baby!
I would say today's breakfast was slightly delayed
Hey, whipping up the scuff is a rally enough!
Still come bump through it endlessly, why?
Take it easy, what did we learn?
Instead of fire in the hearth, let the PC burn out!
Optimistic folks on a quick fix
Teach new dogs all of our old tricks.
Circle-ling stronger than ever and never staying down!
And I'm aware it's ironic
But where's the freaking light?!
Gamerest to streamers, to entertainer-est to them
Now losing you young people
in our hearts, that's priceless!
Spanning new dimensions
we can bring another mystery to light!
Welcoming our ascension, dancing in dark, we ignite!
Show us all we're celebrating
in the myth that we're creating
there's another story waiting
through this world and beyond
Our destined dreams have brought a sphere
a strong unyielding bond guiding us endlessly
we'll bring those moments that we hold dear
Time rushes on
and thorny winds may scatter us
we'll keep this promise
When the moments finally arrive
we'll always find the way to reunite
One, two, three!
Light up, spotlight
let's begin, we'll start stage-dried
and shuffle on in!
Ready, seal the show, we're jumping for joy, let's go!
Fortunes of so cute a band
we'll keep on entertaining hand in hand!
It's our greatest moment yet, a spectacle we'll never forget!
We're holding our party from dusk to dawn, the show will go on and on!
Proud of that we're here to stay and spread the news from Tokyo to Broadway!
Gleaming spotlight, get together, we're boogying all night!
Beaming, so bright, now we're feeling alright!
Since the day we met, we've fallen, going strong and we'll keep moving right along!
So, keep on dancing, your fate
nothing can stop us, we're perfect content!
In harmony, no matter where we go, like it's meant to be, don't you know?
We're gonna feel so alive when it all springs. Ready to put on another show!
There's an answer out there somewhere
When the muses whisper "truth or dare?"
The hands of fate play tug-of-war
But no one's keeping score
Stay the course and be tenacious
'Cause the future is a game of chance
The chips are down, but I'm all in
I play until I win!
I'm not gonna give up now
The wheels of fortune circle back around
A new turn in the betting ring;
A maze of outcomes drawn in golden string
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead:
A wild chase,
A frantic pace,
I got to try my luck, I'm spinning fate
Ah… la da da da da da
I'm always spinning fate
Whoah yeah
Spin the roulette, see where it falls
Testing the limits and betting it all—
Round and around, jumping into the circle
Over and over, a test of will
Oh, the game is never easy
And the outcome is a mystery
But these are fates worth betting on,
Their threads unbroken
Called to life by flaxen string,
Casting lots together at the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet
I spin back 'round with every chance I get
The wheel turns and the die is cast,
The time has come for fate to change at last
And if it's black or red, I'm moving up ahead!
A perfect chance, a daring dance
I'll spin this thread of fate with my own hands
Ooh la la la
I'm taking fate into my hands
Whoah, yeah
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
Can't control it anymore, I'm burnin' up red
Crazy thoughts fillin' my head
Tension rising to the top,
Won't look back, I'll never stop,
Blazing, boiling, gettin' hot,
It's your fault, baby
Fever burning up inside,
It can't be contained
Got my heart goin' up in flames
Tell me you can feel the searing heat
Come on and come on I wanna confess,
Baby oh baby I'm gettin' obsessed
Are you gonna run away, or burn up with me?
Crank it up, crank it up, hotter and hotter,
Gonna be wanna be ready for more
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough,
Fanning the flame of love
And now it's taking over
Blazin' fire, make me a believer,
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air.
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever,
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love burn me away
I'm gonna wanna turn it up, I'm burnin' up, can't get enough
Maybe I'm too hot to touch,
It's your fault, baby
I can't hide it anymore, I'm bearing my soul,
Let these flames swallow me whole
This is how we're gonna play;
A dangerous game,
Got your fire runnin' through my veins
Baby, can't you read between the lines?
Look at me, look at me turnin' to ash,
Breakin' me shakin' me makin' me crash
Gonna sear it all away until you're mine
Drivin' me drivin' me drivin' me crazy,
Tellin' me tellin' me what do you mean
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough,
Fanning the flame of love
And now it's taking over
Blazin' fire, make me a believer,
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air.
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever,
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love burn me away
I'm only getting started...
Blazin' fire, show me your illusion
It doesn't matter if it's real or a dream,
Wild desire fueling my delusion,
I want you burning for me!
Blazin' fire, make me a believer,
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air.
Blazin' fire
Can’t control it anymore, I’m burnin’ up red
Crazy thoughts fillin’ my head
Tension rising to the top, won’t look back, I’ll never stop
Blazing, boiling, gettin’ hot, it’s your fault, baby
Fever burning up inside, it can’t be contained
Got my heart goin’ up in flames
Tell me you can feel the searing heat
Come on and come on, I wanna confess, baby, oh baby, I’m gettin’ obsessed
Are you gonna run away, or burn with me?
Crank it up, crank it up, hotter and hotter, gonna be, wanna be ready for more
I’m caught up in heat wave, I’ll never get enough
Fanning the flame of love, and now it’s taking over
Blazin’ fire, make me a believer
I’m gettin’ dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burnin’ like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love burn me away
Blazin’ fire
I’m gonna, wanna turn it up, I’m burnin’ up, can’t get enough
Maybe I’m too hot to touch, it’s your fault, baby
I can’t hide it anymore, I’m bearing my soul
Let these flames swallow me whole
This is how we’re gonna play, a dangerous game
Got your fire runnin’ through my veins
Baby, can’t you read between the lines?
Look at me, look at me turn in’ to ash, break in’ me, shakin’ me, makin’ me crash
Look at me, look at me turnin’ to ash, breakin’ me, shakin’ me, makin’ me crash
Gonna sear it all away until you’re mine
Drivin’ me, drivin’ me, drivin’ me crazy, tell in’ me, tell in’ me what do you mean
Drivin’ me, drivin’ me, drivin’ me crazy, tellin’ me, tellin’ me what do you mean
I’m caught up in heat wave, I’ll never get enough
Fanning the flame of love, and now it’s taking over
Blazin’ fire, make me a believer
I’m gettin’ dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burnin’ like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love burn me away
Blazin’ fire
Gigi Murin
Cecilia Immergreen
Auto fister
CCGG madness, otomos, now listen
CCGG madness, grems, get in position
CCGG madness, orange + green division
Ooh, auto fister
ハイ！ ハイ！ CCGG mad fun
Hai! Hai! CCGG mad fun
gremlin automaton
ハイ！ ハイ！ CCGG mad fun
Hai! Hai! CCGG mad fun
gremlin automaton
Guten tag!
Do you know where the bathroom is?
I’ve been walking around all day and I really need to go
Uh, no
But I’ve seen this new super cute cafe around the corner
They sell tea and baumkuchen
Sorry, I don’t speak German
Oh?
On this day you are cursed to cope
And keep it in your memory
Oh, come on you’re supposed to hope
And let our brand of madness run its course
Take our hand, let’s fly away
Break a leg, now challenge fate
Quick, before your time’s up
Give in and be our playmate
Hop, step, jump, our dreams await
Love yourself, don’t be afraid
Sign just one condition
Give in, release all inhibition
CCGG, CCGG, CCGG madness
Oh, CCGG, CCGG, auto fister
Oh, CCGG, CCGG, come, let’s play
Recently
I’ve just been having so much anxiety
’Cause I can’t find a single manga that I like, like
I like so many different genres
Like romance, romance, and romance
But I still don’t know what to do
Sorry, what were you saying? I was looking at my phone
Ugh!
Oh, come on, can a girl not hope
To lose your heart in reverie?
There’s no way to divert this trope
So, let our brand of madness run its course
Take our hand, let’s fly away
Make a way now, choose a date
Quick, before your time’s up
Give in and be our playmate
Hop, step, jump, our dreams await
Love yourself, don’t be afraid
Live up your ambition
Come on, let go of intuition
CCGG, CCGG, CCGG madness
Oh, CCGG, CCGG, auto fister
Oh, CCGG, CCGG, come and play
Why do you always yell at me all the time? I just don’t get it
’Cause you’re so stupid
Every time I come to you and I’m trying to be really really nice
All you do is talk over me
Well maybe you should have something good to say for once
I have so many good things to say every single day
Literally not a single time, you drive me insane!
You’re so stupid I can’t stand you!
もう一度！
Once more!
All our fun must come to an end
At least you’ve found a friend
So, let us play and stay forever
Now, together
Vaccines, just a little jab
don't worry mate it's not that bad
small price to pay for proven protection
A small price to pay for proven protection
that will save your ass from covid infection
yeah yeah science has done it again
a new solution to the mess we're in
creating a new way to save the planet
so we can get back to our regular habits
but here's the issue and it's quite severe
we need everyone in or the result is clear
the virus will loiter outside your home
try to steal your breath and infect your dome
but if everyone is keen to go get the vax
going to be safe in the face of virus attacks
defend ourselves from known mutations
bring party sensations across the nation
Vaccines, just a little jab
don't worry mate, it's not that bad
small price to pay for proven protection
A small price to pay for proven protection
that will save your ass from covid infection
yeah, yeah, science has done it again
a new solution to the mess we're in
creating a new way to save the planet
so we can get back to our regular habits
but here's the issue and it's quite severe
we need everyone in or the result is clear
the virus will loiter outside your home
try to steal your breath and infect your dome
but if everyone is keen to go get the vax
going to be safe in the face of virus attacks
Well, LA, we wanted to do some LA
call and response, so I'm just gonna say something and then you cheer if you like it, okay?
Okay? The beach!
Woo! Hold life in LA!
Woo! HoloLive LA!
defend ourselves from known mutations
bring party sensations across the nation
We're very excited to be here at HoloLive
Server Skedaddle!
Server Skedaddle! Please all stand!
It is for the July weekend!
It is for the 4th of July weekend!
For the flag!
Please stand up, everyone!
Oh say, can you see
By the dawn's early light, what so proud
By the dawn's early light, what so proudly we hailed
USA! No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
USA! No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Not yet, not yet!
Since you're standing, we want you to do our chant of our chorus, plus stomping to the beat, okay?
So the left side, we want them to be green, and this side, green, orange, green, orange! Do it now!
Quickly. Okay, perfect, perfect, perfect, good.
Okay, okay, okay, stomping, and then we say CCGG, CCGG... Yes.
CCGG! CCGG! CCGG! CCGG! Madness! CCGG! CCGG! CCGG! CCGG!
CCGG! CCGG! CCGG! CCGG! Auto-fist-pump!
CCGG! CCGG! CCGG! CCGG! Madness!
Come, let's play!
Ichoni, together! Everyone together, really fast now! Show, impress us, okay?
CCGG! CCGG! CCGG! CCGG! Madness! CCGG! CCGG! CCGG! CCGG!
Auto-fist-pump! CCGG! CCGG! CCGG! CCGG! Madness!
CCGG! CCGG! CCGG! CCGG! Come, let's play!
Really impressive, guys! That was really, really good! Maybe America is awesome!
USA! USA! USA! USA!
Yeah! They freaking love us again, in America! In America! Well,
for those at home, this is sadly the end of the free section.
So please... There's one more song, actually. The song after this, one more song, one more song, sorry sorry sorry sorry.
Um, but there's the tickets for the streaming ticket down below, so please check them out in the description. Check out the streaming tickets, okay?
Muryou no haishin wa sugini okonau de saigo ni narimasu. Daibu no suzuki wa zehi haishin chiketto wa katte mitene!
All you freaking haters! All you freaking haters! Okay?
Don't hate us for the very last part!
Since this is the very first MC, we want you to be as loud as possible, okay?
So,
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
We will become a bowling ball and a bowling pin,
and we need you to chant Serendipity, right? Okay.
Keep chanting until we go, stop until we're gone.
Don't stop!
Well, one time together, everyone.
Serendipity! Serendipity!
I'll be your asteroid,
bound to gavel and sentenced me to doom,
even though I'm just ruling what you do,
decide which lines become the truth.
No, you never really followed about it that far,
judging me when I can see you've got the same scars,
that's the price that I paid, it's a thief mark,
better pick your sacrifice.
Nail me to your crucifix,
nothing else can fix this, so I'll
take the blame,
see yourself reflected.
Reflected and not corrected, one request is:
Don't be gentle,
don't be kind when you...
When you hook their eyes out, leave them blind.
One requested fuck, I've seen what you do
in private things, all your friends, yeah they know what you really think.
Do you glory the masses? Keep on singing,
point at me in a hurry, we can escape both for the new controversy,
even when I'm buried, hidden in silence,
you'll be wary, please still got you on our mercy.
Nail me to your crucifix,
nothing else can fix this, so I'll
take the blame,
see yourself reflected.
Reflected and not corrected, one request is:
Don't be gentle,
don't be kind when you...
When you...
Hook their eyes out, leave them blind,
bring me down, take me down.
Bring me down, take me down, take me down, one request is...
I see your sins and they're in your soul consumed,
and they ignored, decayed to your core,
I'll never win to you, but within your...
Break, break, break, break, break, break, break, and when I...
Break, break, break, break, break, break, and in your hands...
...to hammer down, you're the nail.
Don't be gentle, don't be kind when you... murder!
Murder! Murder! Hook their eyes out, leave them blind.
Bring me down, take me down, one request is...
Do you love me? (Do you love me? Not again...) One request is... Do you love me?
Do you love me?
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.